Everyone in the world has forgotten The Beatles. Everyone except Jack…
Yesterday is a comedy, fantasy, music film directed by Danny Boyle.
A struggling musician realizes he's the only person on Earth who can remember The Beatles
after waking up in an alternate reality where the group was forgotten.
Jack Malik, played by Himesh Patel.
Ellie Appleton, played by Lily James.
Carol, played by Sophia Di Martino.
Lucy, played by Ellise Chappell.
Sheila Malik, played by Meera Syal.
Nick, played by Harry Michell.
Yesterday is a 2019 jukebox musical romantic comedy film directed by Danny Boyle and
written by Richard Curtis based on a story by Jack Barth and Curtis.
Himesh Patel stars as struggling musician Jack Malik, who suddenly finds himself as the only
person who remembers the Beatles and becomes famous for performing their songs.
The film also stars Lily James, Joel Fry, Ed Sheeran, and Kate McKinnon.
Yesterday was announced in March 2018.
Filming began the following month around England,
particularly Norfolk and Halesworth in Suffolk.
Photography also took place at Wembley Stadium, the
Principality Stadium, and in Los Angeles.
The filmmakers paid $10 million for the rights to use the Beatles' music.
Although none of the band members were involved, Boyle received
approval for the project from them or their families.
Yesterday had its world premiere at the Tribeca Film Festival on 4 May 2019, and was released in
the United Kingdom and the United States on 28 June 2019 by Universal Pictures.
The film grossed $154.6 million worldwide against a
production budget of $26 million.
The film explores themes of musician, pop singer,
liverpool, england, music festival, united kingdom.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.